Can I smoosh your cheeks?
You can.
You are so incredibly cute.
Thank you for playing with my sister.
No problem.
Gotta say, she looks just like you.
Do you like your big sister, Ayaka-chan?
Yeah!
Which one do you like?
Personally, I've been a big fan
of your cool big sister lately.
Hey... come on...
I'm going to protect Aya.
- So cool!
Don't make me do this around my sister!
She says that, but your
sister always plays along.
I seriously respect that about her!
Then do you know about
when she's being lazy?
Tell me, tell me!
See, sometimes she doesn't
want to move from the couch,
so I have to take care of her.
O-Only when I'm tired!
It's pretty rare!
I'd love to meet Lazy-chan.
Fine!
Ugh... Don't wanna move...
But it's time to go home.
Ayaka-chan even came by to pick you up.
Don't wanna!
Get me my tea.
It's right there, though.
She won't cheer up
unless you do what she says.
All right, I've got it!
Tea
Here's your tea.
Say I'm cute...
I want you to say I'm cute, too.
You're such a cute big sister!
I'm not sure what that has to
do with being lazy, though.
Plus, you're more than just cute, big sis.
She isn't changing back, huh?
Now that's dedication to a role.
Episode 5       Summer Vacation
End of Term
Ceremony!
Take all your
personal
belongings
home!!
Rin... you have plans for summer vacation?
Quit snickering!
I want you to call me Rin, too, Senpai.
Man, I just can't get
used to using your name...
So, does Spoiled-chan
have any plans for summer?
That's cheating.
Come on,
how about you try calling me by my name?
You'll wanna run for the hills.
Eiji-san.
Th-That completely backfired...
You just need to get used to it.
Except we're heading
into summer vacation, anyway.
Just give it up, Nanakura.
Or what, are you gonna come see me
during summer vacation or something?
I actually have no plans!
Wow. That's... sad.
We'll hang out a bunch, okay?
Uh... well...
Rin.
Yes?
We've totally lost the prez
and the others, huh?
We have.
I kind of hope we don't find them, either...
Oh, there he is!
W-Where?
Right over there!
Shooting Range
See? Looks just like him!
Wanna win it?
Let's!
I got it!
Here you go.
That's impressive!
All right, let's have Cool-chan try it out.
Jealous?
I'm about to pop like
48 inches of fireworks!
Okay, enough goofing around.
Let's find the rest of the club...
Hang on, Senpai!
L-Look, they've got cotton candy over there!
Come on, cotton candy can wait...
I want some!
Let's go!
Okay, seriously,
we need to find the others
before we enjoy this any more.
L-Look, masks!
Come on, that's bad news.
Nothing gets you in the
festival mood more than masks.
We're not gonna wanna
find them at this rate!
You realize I'm trying
to hold back here, right?
Masks! Let's check out the masks!
Oh, this is the show my
little sister's really into.
I'm gonna buy it for her.
Th-The president!
S-Senpai, put this on!
You can't just hide!
We need to go after Prism Melody!
I'll guide you to your dreams!
Senpai...
You watch Princess Rhythm?
I caught the movie when
it aired yesterday morning.
Let's go over there!
Yeah!
We're your guardians today, ladies,
so make sure to listen, okay?
Her Friend
Moe
Nanakura's Sister
Ayaka
Yeah!
In particular,
listen to the big sister here.
She's the most grown up one.
We'll call her boss!
- Boss!
Please, don't!
Senpai, you need to look after them too.
It's taking everything I've got not to
be tempted by the water slide...
Let's get started!
Do the thing where you throw us in!
Here you go!
You're not supposed to dive!
That is so much fun!
Senpai!
Sorry, Boss!
I'm good now.
I'm in adult mode. I won't be tempted again.
In that case... can you
put some sunscreen on me?
Okay, that's super adult mode!
Come on! Why are you trying to tempt me?!
If you're gonna be that embarrassed,
don't do it!
But... I wanna have fun, too!
Rin... I had no idea!
Okay, the Boss has signed off on it.
And remember, if one of
us gets hurt, all of us do!
- Yeah!
This is no good...
Rin, hide me, please!
You scared me!
The kids keep making me do
the butterfly stroke!
Onee-chan!
Where's Onii-chan?
We wanted to play more.
Aya...
The thing is, he swam so much,
he melted into the water.
I think that's his nose.
I'll fix him up, so you
two go and play, okay?
O-Okay.
Let's go, Moe-chan.
They're gone.
I am so exhausted...
Senpai... I know this is late, but...
Thanks for coming when I
invited you on such short notice.
Well, a big brother can't say
no to his little sister, can he?
Even when it's hard work.
Thank you so much, onii-chan.
Suddenly I'm not tired anymore!
And I know this is coming late, too...
But your swimsuit is really cute, Rin.
R-Really...?
I wasn't sure when to bring it up.
Although,
that felt a bit like complimenting
an actual sister's swimsuit,
which feels gross!
I might have timed it wrong.
You're taking this big
brother thing too seriously!
Much Ado About Nothing Special: Lazy-chan Observation Log
Much Ado About Nothing Special:
Lazy-chan Observation Log
Part 1.
Part 1
Looks like she's not moving again.
I wonder how much more
I can get away with...
Aya... dader dips.
Fang goo.
Chips
You're welcome.
"Dader dips" is potato chips,
and "fang goo" is thank you.
Aya... I want nori salt flavor...
Nori salt...
Yummy!
Pseudo Harem
Pseudo
Harem
And so then I was in the inner tube,
so we were this close! Like this!
And then Senpai was all like...
"Your swimsuit is cute, Rin."
Can you believe it, Megu?!
We've been over this.
A lot. Over the phone, even.
Hey, Onee-chan.
I don't understand this question.
Whatcha got there?
Okay, want me to do it for you?
Yay!
You're spoiling her.
But if Aya hadn't said she
wanted to go to the pool...
You'll have to ask him
out yourself next time.
I can't!
Don't you and Senpai-san
go out all the time, though?
Those are more like... random occurrences...
I didn't exactly invite him!
In that case, maybe you could
have Cool-chan ask him out?
You know, that whole thing.
She says she can't do it either.
How's that work?
Also, that doesn't sound very cool.
I could ask him for you.
Aya-chan... Would you?
Don't put your little sister
up to stuff like that.
S-Senpai!
I'm visiting my grandparents right now!
Way out in the country... let's see...
There aren't any stores!
And I want some ice cream!
Send
Sending...
I sent it! I sent it!
I actually sent it!
Mr. Prop Department
Huh? A video?
Downloading
Visiting the country sounds nice!
I'm jealous you get to travel.
But seriously, watch out for heatstroke.
I know!
I can send you a scary
video to give you chills.
P-Please don't!!!
P-Please don't!
Here's the ocean!
It's pretty, but really hot!
If I get heatstroke, it'd be nice if
you came out here to take care of me.
Now! Send it before you lose your nerve!
New message from Mr. Prop Department
I was so focused on the
video I dropped my ice cream
Oops...
It's hot. I wanna go swimming.
I'll send a video
Shiro-kun, it's been a while.
I'm back again this year.
Hey, Ayaka.
Should I get ice cream or a ramune drink?
Ramune! That's more summery.
Oh, they have ramune-flavored ice cream!
What, you went with ice cream anyway?
If you insist...
This one time, I'll follow your advice!
Wha... What was that?
I was copying my sister.
Okay, let's head to the
mountains behind Grandpa's place.
Gonna catch us some bugs! Yeah!
I wanted to go to the beach...
But I've got my net and everything!
I want you to take me to the beach!
Seriously, what are you doing?!
Copying her!
So, how long are you gonna be in town?
Until the 15th.
You doing anything tomorrow?
You want to play tomorrow too, Shiro-kun?
N-Not exactly...
I won't play with you
unless you ask me properly.
B-Bug catching!
Tomorrow we're going bug catching, got it?!
Look! There's a crab!
Don't need one.
No?
Nah, you can find them anywhere.
Man, this is boring!
And no trunks means I can't go swimming,
so it's super hot...
Want some?
Much Ado About Nothing Special: Lazy-chan Observation Log
Much Ado About Nothing Special:
Lazy-chan Observation Log
Part 2
Part 2.
You've got an important meeting today.
I think we'll go with this necktie!
Am I playing the daddy?
No, you're the doll.
She stopped moving.
Is it because she's a doll?
Wanna play video games?
You're pretty good, Aya.
When she's Lazy-chan,
I can beat her in the
games she usually wins at!
Much Ado About Nothing Special: Lazy-chan Observation Log
Much Ado About Nothing Special:
Lazy-chan Observation Log.
Part 3
Part 3.
She got yelled at for laying around
and making her uniform all wrinkly...
I wonder if I raised you wrong...?
...Where did you hear such a phrase?